https://pbwc.org/privacy-policy/

0
No products in the cart.
Welcome to our privacy policy
Your privacy is critically important to us.
Professional BusinessWomen of California is located at:
2261 Market #1600San Francisco, CA, 94114-1600U.S.A415.857.2923
It is the Professional BusinessWomen of California’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to pbwc.org (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “pbwc.org”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through our website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and Conditions posted on our website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our website. Depending on your activities when visiting our website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Professional BusinessWomen of California collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Professional BusinessWomen of California’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Professional BusinessWomen of California’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Professional BusinessWomen of California may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Professional BusinessWomen of California also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://pbwc.org blog posts. Professional BusinessWomen of California only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Professional BusinessWomen of California’s websites choose to interact with Professional BusinessWomen of California in ways that require Professional BusinessWomen of California to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Professional BusinessWomen of California gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for our mailing list at https://pbwc.org to provide a name and email address.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Links To External Sites
Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
The Professional BusinessWomen of California discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Professional BusinessWomen of California’s behalf or to provide services available at Professional BusinessWomen of California’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Professional BusinessWomen of California’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Professional BusinessWomen of California will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Professional BusinessWomen of California discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Professional BusinessWomen of California believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Professional BusinessWomen of California, third parties or the public at large.
If you are a registered user of https://pbwc.org and have supplied your email address, Professional BusinessWomen of California may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Professional BusinessWomen of California and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Professional BusinessWomen of California takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Aggregated Statistics
Professional BusinessWomen of California may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Professional BusinessWomen of California may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Professional BusinessWomen of California does not disclose your personally-identifying information.
Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, Professional BusinessWomen of California uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Professional BusinessWomen of California uses cookies to help Professional BusinessWomen of California identify and track visitors, their usage of https://pbwc.org, and their website access preferences. Professional BusinessWomen of California visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Professional BusinessWomen of California’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Professional BusinessWomen of California’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Professional BusinessWomen of California’s use of cookies.
E-commerce
Those who engage in transactions with Professional BusinessWomen of California – by purchasing Professional BusinessWomen of California’s services or products, or making a donation to our organization, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Professional BusinessWomen of California collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Professional BusinessWomen of California. Professional BusinessWomen of California does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Professional BusinessWomen of California may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Professional BusinessWomen of California’s sole discretion. Professional BusinessWomen of California encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
LOCATION + CONTACT 2261 Market #1600
San Francisco, CA 94114-1600
info@pbwc.org
415-857-2923
RECENT TWEETS
What happens when women business leaders step into venture investing? Join @Portfolia October 20th @ 12:00 pm PT an… https://t.co/5cr3tXzVqd
18 hours ago
PBWC is thrilled to welcome Nicole Soluri, past Board Chair and President, to our leadership team as Chief Executiv… https://t.co/L65cUOrQUQ
3 days ago
Hear how the Most Influential Women in Bay Area Business lead in crisis and pay it forward. PBWC Media Partner… https://t.co/NUwOf6oqhA
4 days ago
RECENT NEWSNicole Soluri Named CEO of Professional BusinessWomen of CaliforniaOctober 7, 2020The Legacy of Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader GinsburgSeptember 19, 2020PBWC President and Board Chair Reflects on PBWC’s 31st Annual ConferenceSeptember 8, 2020100th Anniversary of the Ratification of the 19th AmendmentAugust 18, 2020Kaiser Permanente and Professional BusinessWomen of California Event Promotes Career Development and Equal Opportunity in the WorkplaceAugust 11, 2020
GET INVOLVED
Help us realize our vision of a fairer future
Donate
Subscribe to our email list to receive PBWC updates
© 2020 Professional BusinessWomen of California (PBWC)
Privacy Policy
